sweetjack.com 2016-06-08

# Sweet Deals: Daily Deals With Great Discount Rates

Thank you for visiting incentrev.com, an INCENTREV, Inc. site, and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Website unless you choose to provide that information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by INCENTREV, Inc., [www.incentrev.com](http://www.incentrev.com/), [ www.incentrevauctions.com](http://www.incentrevauctions.com/) or any of the sub-domains of either incentrev.com or incentrevauctions.com (collectively "INCENTREV") are governed by this Privacy Policy and Notice. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the INCENTREV.

* * *

###  The Information We Collect

Through INCENTREV's marketing, direct sales, websites, sub-domains and other media, you can bid on or purchase gift certificates, goods, or services. You are able to visit much of this website and enjoy INCENTREV without providing any personally identifiable information. Sometimes, however, we do need your personally identifiable information to provide you with the gift certificates, products and services that you request. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include, but are not limited to: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At some INCENTREV sites and sub-domains and through certain promotions, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might register a person's name and e-mail address to be user of INCENTREV. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, title, e-mail address, and telephone number.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. The server on which the Website is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, and the pages and images requested. We also request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (such as name and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. The contact information may be passed on to the station and used to notify you of other promotions. It may also be passed on to the merchant from whom you bought a certificate or other product. We will not sell, share or otherwise disclose this information to parties not disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Please note that if any government agency legally requests our customer information, we are obligated to release it.

* * *

###  How We Use the Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our gift certificates, goods or services, assist in transactions, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, bids, when you have mad a purchase, or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

If you choose to submit content we may publish your name, screen name, and other information you have provided to us.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Agents and contractors of INCENTREV who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for INCENTREV.

We may transfer your personally identifiable information to other INCENTREV affiliates or partners or to offices for internal management and administrative purposes. Your personal data will be transferred to other INCENTREV offices where necessary for the performance or conclusion of our contractual obligations to you or for your benefit. Transfers of personally identifiable information may also be made where necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

* * *

###  Privacy Options

If an INCENTREV site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by INCENTREV who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from companies not owned by INCENTREV, please write to the address below with the subject "No Third Party Marketing".

**Young Children**  
The Website is not directed to children less than eighteen (18) years of age, and children under such age must not use the website or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves. INCENTREV is not designed to attract anyone under age 18, has no intention of collecting personal information from children, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. INCENTREV will use reasonable efforts to delete such information from its database. This Website complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA).

* * *

###  Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

The INCENTREV sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy notice does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs).

**Cookies**  
To enhance your online experience we use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings, and advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Similarly, as part of an arrangement with our business partners (including, those who present or serve the advertisements that you see on our web pages) we may also access cookies placed by others and allow others to access certain cookies placed by us.

We may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. For more information regarding cookies, please click here.

* * *

###  Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect. INCENTREV is serious about protecting your privacy and we take precautions to safeguard your information. When customers submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. Sensitive information (such as a credit card number), is encrypted and protected with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL is known as the best encryption software in the industry. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

#####  How You Can Access or Correct Information

To inquire about personally identifiable information that this INCENTREV site has collected about you, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us at info@incentrev.com.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

* * *

###  Changes to this Notice

This Notice may be changed by INCENTREV. The revised Notice will be posted to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

* * *

###  How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the INCENTREV Privacy Notice or its implementation please contact us via email at info@incentrev.com or at the following address:

3280 Peachtree Road, NW  
Suite 2300  
Atlanta, Georgia 30305

This Privacy Notice was revised 03/05/2009.
